<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Piyush Thakur</title>
    <link>https://cosmo3769.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Piyush Thakur</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright><atom:link href="https://cosmo3769.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://cosmo3769.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cosmo3769.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>About Me Hello! It&amp;rsquo;s me, Piyush. :)
I am a full stack web developer, and a deep learning practitioner. I work as a freelancer, assisting clients with large-scale cross-platform software projects. I work as an independent contractor at Weights and Biases writing and publishing reports on deep learning topics. I contribute to open source projects, with a current focus on keras projects. Here is my GitHub Profile showing all my contributions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://cosmo3769.github.io/posts/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cosmo3769.github.io/posts/</guid>
      <description>Posts Weights and Biases Q-Learning: Implementation Part
What is Q-Learning?
A Gentle Introduction to Retrieval Augmented Generation (RAG)
Sentiment Analysis with Bag of Tricks
Real Time Social Distance Detector
Personal A Tour Of Policy Gradients </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://cosmo3769.github.io/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cosmo3769.github.io/projects/</guid>
      <description>Projects Community Contributions Cloud Community Days Kolkata 2022 Website This event website was built for the Google Developer Groups Cloud Kolkata community that hosted the biggest developer conclave in Eastern India.
Website
GitHub
Valuable Contributors
Winter of Code 2021 Website This event website was created for the Google Developer Student Clubs NSEC community in order to raise awareness of open source initiatives such as Google Summer of Code.
Website
GitHub</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://cosmo3769.github.io/talks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cosmo3769.github.io/talks/</guid>
      <description>Talks Hands-on git and GitHub: Day 1 YouTube Co-speaker - Ayush
Hands-on git and GitHub: Day 2 YouTube Co-speaker - Ayush</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
